# Gregory Oxsen

### Work Statement

I use the power of user research and design to drive measurable impacts.

### Skills Overview

#### User Research

Conduct qualitative research using designs/prototypes with customers to discover actionable insights. Run moderated and unmoderated usability studies with benchmark criteria to test user comprehension and behaviors involving current product/new features. Monitor quantitative post-launch results to ensure they align with expectations set by qualitative insights.

#### Interaction Design / Front-end

Create Figma/CSS prototypes to create design solutions and validate userflows.

#### Accessibility

Expert on visual success criterion under WCAG 2.0 and WCAG 2.1.

# Work Experience

#### **Emcee Studios**

Oct 2022 - January 2024 Lead Product Designer

#### Freelance

April 2022 - September 2022 Product Designer + Web Developer for Kirellinc.com

#### The RealReal

Feb 2019 - March 2022 Lead Product Designer, Growth

#### HP Enterprise / Micro Focus

Jan 2017 - Feb 2019 Senior UI/UX Designer

#### Clear Digital (formerly WebEnertia)

Feb 2014 - Dec 2016 Senior UI/UX Designer

## Contact

gregoxsen.com / gregoryoxsen@gmail.com 408.660.6119

#### References

Valerie Ouano Lead UX Designer, Apple via AMP Agency 408.550.4379

Vik Salivahanan Senior Product Manager, Flexport 716.534.1556

Daniel Millan Senior Brand Designer, Netlify 599.824.5266

#### Education

San Jose State University 2007-2011 Bachelor of Arts, Design Studies